[   
    {
        "id" : 1,
        "question" : "What is the 2020-2021 membership theme for FBLA?",
        "answer" : "Aspire",
        "options" : ["Aspire","Dream", "Hard work makes the dream work", "Chase your goals"],
        "qType" : "mc"  
    },

    {
        "id" : 2,
        "question" :"Where is nationals this year?",
        "answer" : "Anaheim",
        "options" : ["Anaheim","Chicago", "Atlanta", "Seattle"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 3,
        "question" : "The first line of the FBLA creed is: I believe education is the right of every person",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 4,
        "question" : "Which attire is acceptable for FBLA activities",
        "answer" : "Formal Business Attire",
        "options" : ["Business Casual", "Formal Business Attire","Casual", "Black Tie Only"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 5,
        "question" :"What charitable organization does FBLA primarily support?",
        "answer" : "March of Dimes",
        "options" : ["American Heart Association", "March of Dimes","Feed My Starving Children", "FBLA Scholarship Foundation"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 6,
        "question" :"The parliamentary procedures that FBLA follows come from Richard's Rules",
        "answer" : "False",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
        },

    {
        "id" : 7,
        "question" :"The concept of FBLA was developed at what university?",
        "answer" : "Columbia",
        "options" : ["Columbia","Harvard", "Boston College", "UPenn"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 8,
        "question" :"FBLA was first created by a group of talented high schoolers.",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True", "False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 9,
        "question" :"When is American Enterprise Day?",
        "answer" : "November 15.",
        "options" : ["January 16", "February 22", "May 3", "November 15."],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 10,
        "question" :"When is National Community Service Day?",
        "answer" : "February 15.",
        "options" : ["January 16", "October 9","February 15.", "June 8"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 11,
        "question" :"Dr. Hamden L. Forkner developed the concept of FBLA",
        "answer" : " True",
        "options" : [" True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 12,
        "question" :"Number of FBLA members in 13,000 chartered chapters in the United States, Puerto Rico, Bermuda, the Virgin Islands, Guam, the Cayman Islands, and the Department of the Defense Schools worldwide.",
        "answer" : "250,000",
        "options": [],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {   "id" : 13,
        "question" :"The number of administrative regions FBLA-PBL is divided into.",
        "answer" : "5",
        "options": [],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 14,
        "question" :"FBLA-PBL Week is held during this month.",
        "answer" : "February",
        "options" : ["March", "February","October", "May"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 15,
        "question" :"The official national website address of FBLA-PBL",
        "answer" : "www.fbla-pbl.org",
        "options" : ["www.fbla.org","www.fbla-pbl.org", "www.fblapbl.org", "www.pbl-fbla.org"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {   
        "id" : 16,
        "question" :"The location where the first FBLA local chapter was organized is",
        "answer" : "Johnson City",
        "options" : ["Philadelphia", "Johnson City", "Kenosha", "New York City"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 17,
        "question" :"The minimum number of members required to start a new/reactivated chapter in FBLA-ML.",
        "answer" : "3",
        "options" :[],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 18,
        "question" :"A formal proposal by a member suggesting that the assembly take a certain action is called a: ",
        "answer" : "Motion",
        "options" : ["Call", "Request", "Amendment", "Motion"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    
    },

    {
        "id" : 19,
        "question" :"The chapter officer who prepares and reads the minutes of meetings is called the: ",
        "answer" : "Secretary",
        "options" : ["Secretary","Vice President", "Note Taker", "Scribe"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 20,
        "question" :"The chapter officer who assists the president in the discharge of duties and presides at the meetings in the absence of the president",
        "answer" : "Vice President",
        "options" : ["Assistant to the President","Vice President", "Quorum Keeper", "Secretary"],
        "qType" : "dd"
   
    },

    {
        "id" : 21,
        "question" :"Any summary of principles or opinions professed or adhered to is called a:",
        "answer" : "Creed",
        "options" : ["Promise", "Pledge", "Creed", "Profession"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    
    },

    {
        "id" : 22,
        "question" :"National Officers announced every year at the Awards of Excellence Program at the National Leadership Conference",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 23,
        "question" :"How many events can you compete in per year in FBLA?",
        "answer" : "1",
        "options":[],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 24,
        "question" :"The 2017/2018 national membership theme is: Create Your Future",
        "answer" : "False",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 25,
        "question" :"The event CSA stands for: ",
        "answer" : "Community Service Achievement",
        "options" : ["Community Service Achievement", "Communications Efficiency Assessment", "Computer Science Application", "Curtain Silly Alphabet"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 26,
        "question" :"How many people from each state are eligible to compete at nationals in a given event?",
        "answer" : "4",
        "options":[],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 27,
        "question" :"Every fall, the National Fall Leadership Conference is held in three cities.",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 28,
        "question" :"How many total elected national officers are there?",
        "answer" : "8",
        "options":[],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 29,
        "question" :"Every spring, each state hosts a competition called: ",
        "answer" : "State Leadership Conference",
        "options" : ["Business Leaders Competition", "State FBLA Demonstrations", "FBLA State Conference", "State Leadership Conference"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 30,
        "question" :"How many people from each chapter can compete in a given competitive event?",
        "answer" : "3",
        "options" : [],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 31,
        "question" :"The CEO of FBLA is: ",
        "answer" : "Jean Buckley",
        "options" : ["Frederick Douglass", "Mariam Forner", "William Brighton", "Jean Buckley"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 32,
        "question" :"There are over __ competitive events in FBLA?",
        "answer" : "60",
        "options" : [],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 33,
        "question" :"The BAA program stands for: ",
        "answer" : "Business Achievement Awards",
        "options" : ["Business Acclimation Association","Business Achievement Awards", "Business Ability Assessment", "Blue Atrocious Apple"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 34,
        "question" :"The Parliamentary Procedure competitive event is used to choose the National Parliamentarian",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 35,
        "question" :"The National President is a member of the executive board and is voted on by state voting delegates",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 36,
        "question" :"The FBLA division for the youngest members is: ",
        "answer" : "FBLA-ML",
        "options" : ["FBLA-YL","FBLA-ML", "FBLA-MS", "FBLA-Prep"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 37,
        "question" :"States have the opportunity to have a State Fall Leadership Conference in the fall",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : [ "True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 38,
        "question" :"How many national officers can run for national office from each state per year?",
        "answer" : "1",
        "options" : [],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 39,
        "question" :"How old is FBLA?",
        "answer" : "81",
        "options" : [],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 40,
        "question" :"PBL stands for:",
        "answer" : "Phi Beta Lambda",
        "options" : ["Purple Blue Leaves", "Professional Business Leaders","Phi Beta Lambda", "Providing Business Leaders"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 41,
        "question" :"When was FBLA founded?",
        "answer" : "1940",
        "options" : [],
        "qType" : "ni"
    },

    {
        "id" : 42,
        "question" :"Hamden L. Forkner founded FBLA.",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 43,
        "question" :"Where are the FBLA headquarters",
        "answer" : "Virginia",
        "options" : ["Florida", "California","Virginia", "New York"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 44,
        "question" :"Which state has the largest FBLA membership?",
        "answer" : "Florida",
        "options" : ["Virginia","Florida", "Illinois", "New York"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 45,
        "question" :"The official FBLA colors are: ",
        "answer" : "Blue and Gold",
        "options" : ["Grey and Blue", "Gold and Green", "Green and Grey", "Blue and Gold"],
        "qType" : "dd"
    },

    {
        "id" : 46,
        "question" :"FBLA members have access to exclusive scholarships",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 47,
        "question" :"FBLA stands for Future Business Leaders of America",
        "answer" : "True",
        "options" : ["True","False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 48,
        "question" :"Which state had the first FBLA chapter?",
        "answer" : "Iowa",
        "options" : ["Tennesese","Iowa", "Colorado", "Illinois"],
        "qType" : "mc"
    },

    {
        "id" : 49,
        "question" :"Alexandria Graham is the president and chief executive officer of FBLA",
        "answer" : "False",
        "options" : ["True", "False"],
        "qType" : "tf"
    },

    {
        "id" : 50,
        "question" :"What is the smallest grade you have to be to be a part of FBLA?",
        "answer" : "5",
        "options" : [],
        "qType" : "ni"
    }
]